Luz Marina Rodriguez Papers, 1945-2006
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS
  - Originals and master copies - CLOSED, see Box 8 for use copies
    - Latina Round Table on Health and Reproductive Rights Symposium ( 5 DVDs and 5 camcorder cassette tapes)March, 1998
      - #5 Continuation of Workgroup Reports African, Native American.. Discussion: Timeline/criteria for concept papers measurement tools (Box 9)
    - Luz Rodriguez reads from her work (2 DVDs)undated (Box 9)
    - SisterSong (8 microcassettes, 1 VHS, 7 camcorder videocassettes, 17 DVDs)
      - A. Love - Re-Cap on Day 1 - On racism (Box 10)
      - First training workshop for information on the project SisterSong, group for reproductive rights. Carmen Zorrilla, San Juan PR, March 1999 (Box 10)
      - Grants Administration 1, undated (Box 10)
      - Human Rights 101-11, Loretta Ross, undated (Box 10)
      - RTI/SH Training, Dallas TX, Last day and farewells, undated (Box 10)
      - RTI 202 [tapes 1 and 2], undated (Box 10)
      - Self -Help Intro, undated (Box 10)
      - Copies of microcassettes # 1-5 (Box 10)